<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Últimas Noticias de Fórmula 1 -RSS-</title>
    <link>index.html</link>
    <description>Descubre las últimas noticias, actualizaciones y análisis sobre el mundo de la Fórmula 1, incluyendo resultados de carreras, fichajes y más.</description>
    <language>es</language>

    <item>
      <title>Racing Bulls announce technical team changes ahead of 2025 F1 season</title>
      <link>https://www.formula1.com/en/latest/article/racing-bulls-announce-technical-team-changes-ahead-of-2025-f1-season.3pIvvHQdsaQkiwDAANe8il</link>
      <description>Racing Bulls have announced that their Technical Director, Jody Egginton, will be leaving the team after more than 10 years as part of the operation.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>Daniel M.R</author>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Hulkenberg praises 'fast as hell' rookie team mate Bortoleto as he assesses Kick Sauber's pre-season</title>
      <link>https://www.formula1.com/en/latest/article/hulkenberg-praises-fast-as-hell-rookie-team-mate-bortoleto-as-he-assesses.6XjGMlFX034K4sBZ2bXoje</link>
      <description>Nico Hulkenberg has shared some words of praise for new team mate Gabriel Bortoleto following pre-season testing, with the German stating that the rookie is “fast as hell” as they begin working together at Kick Sauber.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>Daniel M.R</author>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>IN NUMBERS: The incredible figures behind seven seasons of Drive to Survive</title>
      <link>https://www.sprudge.com/sustainable-coffee-shops.html</link>
      <description>Formula 1 fans get to enjoy a post-testing treat this week as the seventh season of Drive to Survive lands on Netflix. But just how much goes into producing a show that follows all 10 teams and 20 drivers around the world year in, year out? With help from the talented team at production company Box To Box, F1.com runs through some key numbers…</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>Daniel M.R</author>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>‘We had one shot to get it right’ – Susie Wolff on the ‘F1 ACADEMY effect’ and the crucial next steps for the future</title>
      <link>https://www.formula1.com/en/latest/article/we-had-one-shot-to-get-it-right-susie-wolff-on-the-f1-academy-effect-and-the.7zkKBr5hx6joEAPLvYPapF</link>
      <description>Changing perceptions of a woman’s place in motorsport and funnelling the next generation of female talent towards Formula 1 was never going to be an overnight fix.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>Daniel M.R</author>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
